

MOHAMED DAWAH

CONTACT INFO

I'm A Resident and Eligible to work in poland.

- +48538278499
- M.dawah94@gmail.com
- Katowice. Poland
- My Website

modawah.github.io/portofilio

EDUCATION

2012-2017

bachelor degree of social work Delta university

web development deploma udacity

LANGUAGES

English

Arabic

polish

PROFILE

Highly accurate data entry with 2 years experience,

high Typing Speed with zero errors.

Maintained 99% accuracy in two fast-paced data entry positions. Used MS Office daily, including Outlook and Excel.

Devised several MS Excel macros to automate repetitive tasks. Increased efficiency by 33%.

Computer and technical skills (including software knowledge).

Organisational and time management abilities.

Administrative skills.

Communication (written and verbal).

EXPERIENCE

2016-2018 **SELLER**

GROCERY STORE serving customers, ordering and restocking the

products

2018-2020 **DATA ENTRY**

IREM.S.P.A

office works (excel, word and powerpoint). (ZOHR GAS FIELD PROJECT)

daily productivity reports.

archiving and files managemnt.

using company server's software to store data.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

MS OFFICE HTML **EXCEL** CSS WORD **JAVASCRIPT POWERPOINT BOOTSTRAP**

INTEREST

sport </>coding reading gaming